<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>The Unbound Nomad - Blog</title><link href="https://www.unboundnomad.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://www.unboundnomad.com/feeds/blog.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://www.unboundnomad.com/</id><updated>2024-01-13T20:55:00+00:00</updated><entry><title>Stay Safe and Prepared: 10 Tips for Riding Your Motorcycle in the Rain</title><link href="https://www.unboundnomad.com/blog/stay-safe-ride-hard.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-03-19T16:40:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-03-19T16:40:00+00:00</updated><author><name>The Unbound Nomad</name></author><id>tag:www.unboundnomad.com,2023-03-19:/blog/stay-safe-ride-hard.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;h1&gt;Stay Safe and Prepared: 10 Tips for Riding Your Motorcycle in the Rain&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Riding a motorcycle in the rain can be challenging and risky, but with the right preparation and safety measures, you can enjoy the ride without compromising your well-being. As motorcycle enthusiasts, we understand the thrill and joy …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h1&gt;Stay Safe and Prepared: 10 Tips for Riding Your Motorcycle in the Rain&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Riding a motorcycle in the rain can be challenging and risky, but with the right preparation and safety measures, you can enjoy the ride without compromising your well-being. As motorcycle enthusiasts, we understand the thrill and joy of hitting the open road and feeling the wind in our hair. However, riding in wet weather requires a different set of skills and precautions to keep yourself and others safe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this article, we provide 10 essential tips to help you stay safe and prepared while riding in the rain, from checking your motorcycle before hitting the road to knowing when to pull over. Whether you're a new rider or an experienced one, these tips will give you expert advice and practical recommendations for a safe and enjoyable ride in the rain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before we dive into the tips, let's talk about why riding in the rain can be challenging and the importance of being prepared. Rain affects visibility, road conditions, and your motorcycle's performance, making it more difficult to control and navigate. It's essential to be proactive and take the necessary precautions to ensure your safety and avoid accidents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, without further ado, let's get started on our 10 tips for riding your motorcycle in the rain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Tip 1: Check your motorcycle&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rain or shine, it's essential to check your motorcycle before hitting the road. However, checking your motorcycle is especially crucial when riding in the rain. Wet weather can make road conditions more treacherous and increase the likelihood of accidents. A well-maintained motorcycle can make all the difference in staying safe and avoiding accidents in wet weather.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To prepare your motorcycle for a rainy ride, start by ensuring that your tires have adequate tread depth and are inflated to the correct pressure. Check your brakes to make sure they are in good condition and that your brake pads are not worn down. It's also a good idea to check your lights, including your headlights, taillights, and turn signals, to ensure that they are working correctly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to these essential checks, consider using a rain cover for your air filter and chain to protect them from getting wet. Water can get into the air filter, causing it to clog and impairing engine performance. Wet chains can also cause rust and damage, so it's important to protect them from the rain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Call to action: Always do a pre-ride inspection, especially in wet weather. Taking the time to check your motorcycle before hitting the road can help prevent accidents and ensure that your ride is safe and enjoyable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Tip 2: Dress appropriately&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it comes to riding in the rain, wearing the right gear can make all the difference. Not only does proper rain gear keep you dry and comfortable, but it can also improve your visibility to other drivers on the road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explanation of how rain gear works - Rain gear is designed to be       waterproof and windproof, keeping you dry and warm in wet weather.       There are a variety of rain gear options available, from full rain       suits to jackets and pants made specifically for wet weather riding.     It's important to choose gear that is breathable and allows for       ventilation to prevent sweating.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Importance of wearing proper gear - In addition to keeping you dry and comfortable, wearing proper gear can also protect you in case       of an accident. Waterproof gear can prevent your clothes from getting    wet and heavy, which can impede your movement and reaction time on       the bike. Additionally, bright and reflective rain gear can make you     more visible to other drivers on the road, reducing the risk of       accidents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Suggestions for the right clothing and accessories - When choosing rain gear, look for items that are made specifically for       motorcycle riding and that offer features such as waterproof zippers,    adjustable cuffs and hems, and reflective detailing. Consider       purchasing a helmet with a built-in visor or anti-fog inserts to       improve your visibility in wet conditions. Other useful accessories      for wet weather riding include waterproof gloves, boot covers, and       neck warmers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Call to action: Invest in quality rain gear - Don't skimp on rain gear - investing in high-quality, properly fitting gear can make all the difference in your comfort and safety while riding in the rain. Be sure to check your gear before each ride to ensure that it's still in good condition and that zippers and seams are sealed. Remember, staying dry and visible is key to staying safe on the road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Tip 3: Slow down&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Riding at high speeds in wet weather can be dangerous and risky. Rain can significantly affect visibility and road conditions, making it hard to control your motorcycle. Therefore, it is essential to slow down and ride at a safe speed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it comes to braking and accelerating in the rain, it's crucial to be gentle and smooth. Abrupt or sudden movements can cause your tires to lose traction, leading to a loss of control or even a crash.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are a few tips for braking and accelerating in the rain:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Increase your following distance and give yourself plenty of time to stop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brake gently and smoothly, avoiding sudden or hard braking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be extra cautious when accelerating, especially when starting from a stop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoid sudden movements and be gentle on the throttle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember, it's always better to arrive at your destination safely, even if it takes a little longer. So, slow down and enjoy the ride while staying safe in wet weather.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Call to action: Always ride at a safe speed in the rain, and be extra gentle and smooth when braking and accelerating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Tip 4: Avoid standing water&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Riding through standing water can be one of the most dangerous challenges of riding in the rain. Water on the road can cause your tires to lose traction and potentially cause an accident. Here are some tips to help you navigate standing water safely:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explanation of the dangers of hydroplaning Hydroplaning is a phenomenon where a layer of water forms between the tires of your motorcycle and the road, causing you to lose control of your bike. This can be extremely dangerous and is one of the biggest risks of riding through standing water.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Importance of avoiding standing water and puddles The best way to avoid hydroplaning is to avoid standing water and puddles altogether. If you see water on the road, slow down and try to navigate around it. Be especially cautious on roads with poor drainage or low spots where water may collect.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tips for navigating wet roads If you can't avoid standing water, try to ride in the tire tracks of the vehicles in front of you. The tracks can be slightly drier and offer better traction. Additionally, try to ride in a straight line and avoid sudden movements, such as swerving or braking, which can cause you to lose control.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Call to action: Stay alert for standing water and adjust your route if necessary Always stay alert for standing water, especially in low-lying areas or near bodies of water. If you can, try to plan your route to avoid roads that are prone to flooding. Remember, the best way to stay safe in the rain is to be prepared and avoid unnecessary risks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Tip 5: Maintain a safe distance&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the most important things you can do when riding in the rain is to maintain a safe following distance. Wet roads can increase your stopping distance, so you need to leave more space between you and the vehicle in front of you. In general, you should aim to stay at least four seconds behind the vehicle in front of you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To calculate your following distance, pick a fixed object on the road, like a sign or a tree. When the vehicle in front of you passes that object, start counting "one thousand one, one thousand two, one thousand three, one thousand four." If you pass the object before you finish counting, you're following too closely and need to increase your distance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's also important to remember that other vehicles may not be able to stop as quickly as you can in wet conditions. This means you should be extra cautious when changing lanes or passing other vehicles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By maintaining a safe following distance, you'll give yourself more time to react to sudden changes in traffic and reduce the risk of a collision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Call to action: Always leave enough space between yourself and other vehicles when riding in the rain. Remember to calculate your following distance by picking a fixed object on the road and counting "one thousand one, one thousand two, one thousand three, one thousand four."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Tip 6: Use proper lighting&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Riding a motorcycle in the rain can greatly reduce your visibility on the road. This is why it's important to use proper lighting to make yourself more visible to other drivers. Your headlights, taillights, and turn signals are especially important in wet weather conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make sure that all of your lights are working properly before you hit the road. You should also clean your lights regularly to remove any dirt or debris that could impair their effectiveness. Consider installing high-visibility bulbs or reflective tape to make your motorcycle more visible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When riding in the rain, always use your headlights, even during the day. This can help you see better, but it also makes you more visible to other drivers. Use your turn signals to indicate your intentions, and be sure to use your brake light to alert other drivers when you are slowing down or coming to a stop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember, your lights are your lifeline when riding in the rain. Without them, you're practically invisible to other drivers. So always make sure they're in good working condition and use them properly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Call to action: Take the time to check your motorcycle's lights and clean them regularly. Use high-visibility bulbs or reflective tape to make yourself more visible to other drivers. Always use your headlights, turn signals, and brake lights when riding in the rain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Tip 7: Watch out for oil and debris&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it's raining, the water can wash oil and debris onto the road, making it even more slippery than it already is. This can be very dangerous for motorcycles, especially when taking turns or braking. Here are some tips to help you avoid oil and debris:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stay alert for hazards: Be aware of your surroundings and scan the road ahead for any oil or debris that may be in your path.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Slow down: Reduce your speed when you see debris or oil on the road. Slow down gradually and try to avoid any sudden movements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoid sudden braking: If you need to brake, apply the brakes gently and progressively. Avoid slamming on the brakes, as this can cause your wheels to lock up and skid.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use your vision: Look ahead and try to spot any potential hazards. Use your peripheral vision to scan the sides of the road as well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use the center of the lane: When riding in wet weather, it's best to ride in the center of the lane to avoid any debris or oil that may be on the sides of the road.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Call to action: Stay alert and avoid hazards in the road by scanning the road ahead, reducing your speed, avoiding sudden braking, and using the center of the lane.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Tip 8: Be extra cautious at intersections&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Intersections can be dangerous in any weather condition, but they can become even more treacherous when it's raining. In wet weather, the roads can become slick, reducing the amount of traction between the tires and the pavement. This can make it harder to stop, accelerate, and turn. Additionally, visibility can be reduced, making it harder to see other vehicles, pedestrians, and traffic signals. Here are some tips for navigating intersections safely in the rain:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Approach intersections with caution When you're approaching an intersection in the rain, it's important to slow down and be extra cautious. Give yourself plenty of time to react to changing traffic signals and other vehicles. Keep in mind that the roads may be slick, so you'll need to give yourself extra time to stop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be alert for other vehicles In wet weather, it can be harder to see other vehicles, so you'll need to be extra vigilant. Look for other cars, trucks, and motorcycles, and be prepared for unexpected movements. Always be ready to stop or maneuver around other vehicles if necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Watch for pedestrians Pedestrians can be harder to see in the rain, so you'll need to be extra cautious when you're approaching crosswalks or other areas where pedestrians might be crossing the road. Look for people carrying umbrellas or wearing raincoats, and be prepared to stop if necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Check traffic signals Traffic signals can be harder to see in the rain, so be sure to check them carefully as you approach intersections. If you're not sure what the signal is indicating, come to a complete stop and wait until you're sure it's safe to proceed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By approaching intersections with caution, being alert for other vehicles and pedestrians, and checking traffic signals carefully, you can navigate intersections safely in wet weather. Remember to give yourself plenty of time to react, and be prepared to adjust your speed or route if conditions become too hazardous.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Tip 9: Stay focused and alert&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Riding a motorcycle in the rain requires extra focus and attention. Wet conditions can reduce your visibility and make it harder to control your bike, so it's important to stay alert and avoid distractions. Here are some tips to help you stay focused while riding in the rain:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoid distractions: Distractions can be dangerous at any time, but they're especially risky in wet weather. Avoid using your phone or other devices while riding and stay focused on the road ahead.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep your eyes moving: Make a habit of scanning the road ahead and checking your mirrors frequently. This will help you stay aware of your surroundings and avoid potential hazards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anticipate other drivers: In wet weather, it's important to anticipate what other drivers might do. Be prepared for sudden stops or turns and give yourself plenty of space to react.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be mindful of fatigue: Riding in the rain can be tiring, so it's important to take breaks when you need them. Stop and rest if you're feeling fatigued, and avoid riding for long periods without taking a break.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember, staying focused and alert is key to staying safe on the road, especially in wet weather. By avoiding distractions, keeping your eyes moving, anticipating other drivers, and taking breaks when needed, you'll be better able to handle the challenges of riding in the rain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Tip 10: Know when to pull over&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While riding in the rain, there may come a point when the conditions become too dangerous to continue. It's important to know when it's time to pull over and wait out the storm. Here are some tips to help you recognize when it's time to pull over:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Heavy rainfall: If the rain is coming down so hard that you can't see the road, it's time to pull over. Heavy rain can make it difficult to see hazards and other vehicles on the road.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flooding: If the road is flooding or there is standing water, it's best to pull over. Not only can standing water cause hydroplaning, but it can also hide hazards in the road.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thunderstorms: If there is lightning, it's best to pull over and wait until the storm passes. Riding in a thunderstorm can be extremely dangerous, especially if lightning strikes near you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Poor visibility: If the rain is making it difficult to see, it's time to pull over. Poor visibility can make it hard to see hazards and other vehicles on the road.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When pulling over, make sure to find a safe place off the road. Look for a rest area, gas station, or other sheltered location. Once you've pulled over, wait until the rain subsides before continuing your ride.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Call to action: Know when it's time to pull over and wait out the rain. Always prioritize your safety over getting to your destination quickly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Riding a motorcycle in the rain can be a challenging experience, but with the right preparation and safety measures, it can also be an enjoyable one. By following the 10 essential tips we've outlined in this article, you can stay safe and prepared while riding in wet weather.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From checking your motorcycle before hitting the road to knowing when to pull over, we've covered everything you need to know to stay safe and enjoy the ride in the rain. Remember to always do a pre-ride inspection, invest in quality rain gear, maintain a safe speed, avoid standing water, maintain a safe distance, use proper lighting, watch out for oil and debris, be extra cautious at intersections, stay focused and alert, and know when to pull over.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By incorporating these tips into your rainy day riding routine, you'll be better equipped to handle the challenges that come with wet weather. So don't let a little rain stop you from enjoying your ride, just make sure you're prepared and safe while doing so. Happy riding!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have questions about preparing for a ride, gear, or conditions, I’m always happy to help you think it through.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin:1rem 0 1.25rem 0;"&gt;
  &lt;a href="https://www.unboundnomad.com/pages/booking.html"
     style="display:inline-block; background-color:#660099; color:#3DA80A;
            padding:0.7rem 1.6rem; border-radius:6px; text-decoration:none;
            font-weight:600;"&gt;
    🌧️ Let’s Talk Rain Riding
  &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Blog"></category><category term="Motorcycles"></category><category term="Lifestyle"></category><category term="Rain"></category><category term="Riding"></category><category term="Gear"></category><category term="Skill"></category></entry><entry><title>Ohio's Windy 9 Tour</title><link href="https://www.unboundnomad.com/blog/ohios-windy-9-tour.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-13T20:43:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-01-13T20:43:00+00:00</updated><author><name>The Unbound Nomad</name></author><id>tag:www.unboundnomad.com,2024-01-13:/blog/ohios-windy-9-tour.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;h1&gt;Ohio's Windy 9 Tour&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9 Thrilling Routes, 1 Great Destination. Ohio’s Windy 9 is a motorcycling destination comprised of 9 routes that begin and end in Athens, Ohio. The abundance of curves and elevation change along these roads make this a popular destination for motorcyclists. This route can be …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h1&gt;Ohio's Windy 9 Tour&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9 Thrilling Routes, 1 Great Destination. Ohio’s Windy 9 is a motorcycling destination comprised of 9 routes that begin and end in Athens, Ohio. The abundance of curves and elevation change along these roads make this a popular destination for motorcyclists. This route can be customized to fit the time you have available so come for 1, ride all 9, or let The Unbound Nomad create a customized package just for you!
&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;The Windy 9&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: left;"&gt;Ride Name&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: center;"&gt;Distance&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: center;"&gt;:&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: left;"&gt;Ride Time&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: left;"&gt;Rim of the World&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center;"&gt;80 miles&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center;"&gt;:&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: left;"&gt;2 hours&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: left;"&gt;Southern Dip&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center;"&gt;94 miles&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center;"&gt;:&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: left;"&gt;2.5 hours&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: left;"&gt;Hocking Hills Nipper&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center;"&gt;93 miles&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center;"&gt;:&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: left;"&gt;2.25 hours&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: left;"&gt;Lazy Rivers&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center;"&gt;98 miles&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center;"&gt;:&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: left;"&gt;2.25 hours&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: left;"&gt;Zaleski Zipper&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center;"&gt;50 miles&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center;"&gt;:&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: left;"&gt;1 hour&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: left;"&gt;Pioneer Pass&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center;"&gt;104 miles&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center;"&gt;:&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: left;"&gt;2.5 hours&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: left;"&gt;Pomeroy Dash&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center;"&gt;56 miles&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center;"&gt;:&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: left;"&gt;1.5 hours&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: left;"&gt;Black Diamond Run&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center;"&gt;103.5 miles&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center;"&gt;:&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: left;"&gt;2.5 hours&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: left;"&gt;Tripple Nickel&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center;"&gt;91.5 miles&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center;"&gt;:&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: left;"&gt;2.25 hours&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Interested in This Ride?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p style="margin:1rem 0 1.25rem 0;"&gt;
  &lt;a href="https://www.unboundnomad.com/pages/booking.html"
     style="display:inline-block; background-color:#660099; color:#3DA80A;
            padding:0.7rem 1.6rem; border-radius:6px; text-decoration:none;
            font-weight:600;"&gt;
    🏍️ Plan This Ride
  &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style="font-size:0.95rem; margin-top:0.3rem;"&gt;
  When you reach out, mention &lt;strong&gt;“Ohio's Windy 9 Tour”&lt;/strong&gt; and let me know your
  approximate dates, starting point, and how many riders you expect.
&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Blog"></category><category term="Motorcycles"></category><category term="Lifestyle"></category></entry><entry><title>Devil's Tower Tour</title><link href="https://www.unboundnomad.com/blog/devils-tower-tour.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-13T20:55:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-01-13T20:55:00+00:00</updated><author><name>The Unbound Nomad</name></author><id>tag:www.unboundnomad.com,2024-01-13:/blog/devils-tower-tour.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;!-- ========================= --&gt;
&lt;!--      CINEMATIC HERO       --&gt;
&lt;!-- ========================= --&gt;

&lt;div style="
  position:relative;
  width:100%;
  height:380px;
  overflow:hidden;
  border-radius:0;
  margin-bottom:2.5rem;
"&gt;

  &lt;!-- Background Image --&gt;
  &lt;img src="https://www.unboundnomad.com/images/devilsTower.png"
       alt="Devil's Tower Tour Hero"
       style="
         width:100%;
         height:100%;
         object-fit:cover;
         object-position:center;
         display:block;
       "&gt;

  &lt;!-- Dark Overlay --&gt;
  &lt;div style="
    position:absolute;
    top:0;
    left:0;
    width:100%;
    height:100%;
    background:rgba(0,0,0,0.45);
    backdrop-filter:blur(1px);
  "&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;!-- Title Text --&gt;
  &lt;div style="
    position:absolute;
    bottom:40px;
    left:50%;
    transform:translateX(-50%);
    text-align:center;
    color:white;
    padding:0 1rem;
  "&gt;
    &lt;h1 style="
      margin:0;
      font-size:2.75rem;
      font-weight:700;
      text-shadow:0 4px 12px rgba(0,0,0,0.6);
    "&gt;
      Devil's Tower Tour
    &lt;/h1&gt;

    &lt;p style="
      margin:0.8rem 0 0 0;
      font-size:1.15rem;
      font-weight:400;
      opacity:0.9;
      text-shadow:0 3px 8px rgba(0,0,0,0.5);
    "&gt;
      An unforgettable motorcycle experience.
    &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Devil's Tower Tour&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p height="531" style="display: block; margin: 0 auto" width="500"&gt;Traveling from Sturgis to Devils Tower and back, this route takes you from a great area in South Dakota to a great area in Wyoming. The route is full of long sweeping curves that take you through diverse scenery including …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;!-- ========================= --&gt;
&lt;!--      CINEMATIC HERO       --&gt;
&lt;!-- ========================= --&gt;

&lt;div style="
  position:relative;
  width:100%;
  height:380px;
  overflow:hidden;
  border-radius:0;
  margin-bottom:2.5rem;
"&gt;

  &lt;!-- Background Image --&gt;
  &lt;img src="https://www.unboundnomad.com/images/devilsTower.png"
       alt="Devil's Tower Tour Hero"
       style="
         width:100%;
         height:100%;
         object-fit:cover;
         object-position:center;
         display:block;
       "&gt;

  &lt;!-- Dark Overlay --&gt;
  &lt;div style="
    position:absolute;
    top:0;
    left:0;
    width:100%;
    height:100%;
    background:rgba(0,0,0,0.45);
    backdrop-filter:blur(1px);
  "&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;!-- Title Text --&gt;
  &lt;div style="
    position:absolute;
    bottom:40px;
    left:50%;
    transform:translateX(-50%);
    text-align:center;
    color:white;
    padding:0 1rem;
  "&gt;
    &lt;h1 style="
      margin:0;
      font-size:2.75rem;
      font-weight:700;
      text-shadow:0 4px 12px rgba(0,0,0,0.6);
    "&gt;
      Devil's Tower Tour
    &lt;/h1&gt;

    &lt;p style="
      margin:0.8rem 0 0 0;
      font-size:1.15rem;
      font-weight:400;
      opacity:0.9;
      text-shadow:0 3px 8px rgba(0,0,0,0.5);
    "&gt;
      An unforgettable motorcycle experience.
    &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Devil's Tower Tour&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p height="531" style="display: block; margin: 0 auto" width="500"&gt;Traveling from Sturgis to Devils Tower and back, this route takes you from a great area in South Dakota to a great area in Wyoming. The route is full of long sweeping curves that take you through diverse scenery including mountains, meadows and Devils Tower National Monument. The wide open roads are in good condition with gradual climbs and turns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Interested in This Ride?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p style="margin:1rem 0 1.25rem 0;"&gt;
  &lt;a href="https://www.unboundnomad.com/pages/booking.html"
     style="display:inline-block; background-color:#660099; color:#3DA80A;
            padding:0.7rem 1.6rem; border-radius:6px; text-decoration:none;
            font-weight:600;"&gt;
    🏍️ Plan This Ride
  &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style="font-size:0.95rem; margin-top:0.3rem;"&gt;
  When you reach out, mention &lt;strong&gt;“Devil's Tower Tour”&lt;/strong&gt; and let me know your
  approximate dates, starting point, and how many riders you expect.
&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Blog"></category><category term="Motorcycles"></category><category term="Lifestyle"></category><category term="Adventure"></category><category term="Tours"></category></entry></feed>